# **Andy Tripathy**

Waterloo, ON N2L 3G1 a28tripa@uwaterloo.ca +16478290085

Hi there! I'm Andy, a 2nd year student in Business and Design at University of Waterloo. I am learning to specialize in digital designing, social media marketing, content creation, and collaborative production management. My relevant tech skills are MS Excel, PowerPoint, and Word. I am also skilled in Adobe Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop, and Premiere Pro/Rush. I have gained relevant work experience from interning at Procor and Vector Marketing. As for my skillsets listed at the bottom, I have developed each of those throughout my 4 years of secondary education.

#### Personal Details

Highest Level of Education: Bachelor's Degree

Total years of experience: 1

# Work Experience

#### **Schedule Coordinator**

Great Clips - Oakville, ON March 2023 to August 2023

I warmly greet salon clients, manage check-ins, and handle inquiries with a friendly demeanor. Proficient in phone communication and maintaining a tidy reception area, I collaborate with stylists for smooth operations. Dedicated to cleanliness, I ensure a professional salon experience by keeping the environment organized and welcoming.

#### **Sales Associate**

Vector Marketing - Oakville, ON June 2022 to September 2022

I am skilled in generating leads and scheduling appointments through diverse marketing channels, engaging potential clients interested in kitchen cutlery. Through informative Zoom calls, I showcase our high-quality cutlery products, understanding clients' needs to offer personalized recommendations. Building and maintaining strong client relationships, I address inquiries promptly. Keeping abreast of product knowledge and industry trends, I effectively communicate our cutlery's value proposition. Additionally, I provide accurate and timely reports on sales activities, client feedback, and market insights.

#### Marketing and HR Assistant

Procor Limited - Oakville, ON February 2022 to June 2022

I actively contribute to recruitment and onboarding processes by creating job ads and scheduling interviews. Responsible for maintaining employee records and updating HR databases, I ensure accurate

and organized information. Additionally, I support HR projects and initiatives, including employee engagement activities, to foster a positive workplace environment.

## Education

## Post-secondary education in User Experience (UX-Design)

University of Waterloo - Waterloo, ON August 2023 to Present

## High school diploma or GED

Garth Webb Secondary School - Oakville, ON September 2019 to June 2023

#### Skills

- User Experience (UX)
- User Interface (UI)
- · Fashion design
- · Fashion retail
- Logo design
- Adobe Illustrator
- Typography
- Adobe Premiere
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe After Effects
- Illustration
- · Graphic Design
- Adobe InDesign
- Photography
- Video Production
- Adobe Lightroom
- Branding
- · Video Editing
- Filming
- Layout Design
- Content Development